Did you decide to take the
Don't.
That is far enough to not touch her highness.
Orange.
Oh, bad.
Andalusia leader to all units. Make sure targeting is confined to the transports only. If they launch cataphracts, do not engage.
We will use Kauffman 6 as our anchor for a wire swing by, and then return to Trident base. Good hunting, people.
Roger.
Target located. Squad, commence attack now.
Gravity field's choppy. Our rounds are drifting.
Stay calm. Let's hit them before they can get too close.
Multiple high density satellites. We can't hit them from this far away.
That area. Cover it completely. Keep firing.
Andalusia 3-3. I'm hit. Damage is minor. Continuing the mission.
Andalusia 3-3.
Andalusia 2-2. That's not possible. How can he land any shots in this gravitational flux?
How could they?
Incoming high heat source.
Is it the enemy?
No, sir.
Look, that cataphract.
The Tharsis.
Try and get clear. I'm going to handle them.
That voice. It's their slain Troyard.
Andalusia 3-3.
How can I not be hitting him? I'm more than close enough for that.
The blessings of my Lady Princess of Salem are upon me. Sir Slain Troyard has justly arrived.
How can I not be hitting him?
Since I was young, I have idolized the Earth.
Its blue seas, its blue skies.
That world is blessed with water, air, and sunlight.
Life, and abundant natural resources.
I once almost lost my life on that beautiful blue world.
And then, I saw the reality.
How outrageous it was for the Terrans to live among that bounty without appreciating it.
How they waste resources and destroy nature in their pursuit of pleasure.
We must not let them have their way with this precious world of Earth.
Therefore, I, a Salem verse Alusia, princess of the Verse Empire,
do hereby commend and praise the orbital knights who gave their lives trying to save the Earth from the Terrans.
Why do you bother watching what they're broadcasting?
I'm just curious about a few things.
Like, what's the deal with the princess anyway?
Who knows?
I mean, I thought she was on our side. What happened?
Maybe she just lost hope that there'd ever be peace.
It's only natural she would side with Mars.
She is a Martian, right?
Hey! Hey, Inko!
You got something on your mind?
Huh?
Oh no, nothing important at all.
I was thinking this might be our last chance to relax for a while.
Yeah.
We're due back on board the ship tomorrow, and lift off the day after that.
Hmm.
So he's not what you're thinking about?
Come on! You can't be serious! It's not like that!
Hmm.
Quit standing around and get to work!
Are you guys here to be trained or what?
Y-yes, sir!
PFC Craftman!
Would you mind looking at this?
Oh yeah, the slate near transport.
So, what's the problem?
I didn't think there were any KG-6's assigned to this ship.
Is the info on this manifest right?
Yeah, we're gonna want this.
They'll trash it right away anyhow.
So...
Get it stowed. Where it can be accessed quickly.
Lift off is scheduled for the day after tomorrow.
Any troops that may arrive late should still make it.
By any chance, are you referring to him?
I have to wonder what the top brass have in mind for this.
Seems like they're sending us into battle with their vitals exposed.
If those vitals are competent enough, we'll be okay.
We're told to use him as effectively as we can.
And that's not just for him. That goes for all of us.
They can't rely on a ship that might stop working any minute.
Go cause trouble away from the main force.
That is the mission of this ship and crew.
That makes us pawns scheduled for sacrifice.
Sacrificial pawns have their own special attributes.
You mean how when you lose your main guy, then your side guy gets promoted to be main guy, ma'am?
If you ever lose your main guy, then you look around for a new main guy.
A side guy is always a side guy.
I never thought that we'd be fighting side by side again.
Roger that, ma'am.
Oh.
Hello.
I don't know.
It's a miracle that he survived.
Impressive landing in such an uneven gravity field as this.
Your skills continue to grow, Sir Slane.
Your compliment honors me greatly, Count Sosbaum.
Granting you the title of knight was a wise decision.
How went the battle?
Four enemy units destroyed.
An inspiring and notable coup, my lord Slane.
Please, stop that, Mr. Harklyte.
There's no need for my lord when you talk with me.
I'm afraid that will not do at all, my lord Slane.
I am your manservant.
Look, you are older and more experienced than I.
Plus the fact that I am not a true Verzean.
That does not change the fact that you are a knight, my lord.
Furthermore, please refrain from using mister with me, my lord.
It is not appropriate.
Enter.
Pardon the interruption.
A good day to you, Princess Lemrina.
Are you well?
You seem in good spirits?
I am weary.
But thank you, Count Sosbaum.
Tell me, how fares our new world out there?
The invasions of North and South America are complete.
Their takeover is underway.
As far as Eurasia and the Far East,
due to the surrender of the landing castles there,
UFE counterattacks continue.
How long before I am able to go down and see the earth?
We project that the UFE will be exhausted soon.
Once that has happened,
you, who inherit the bloodline of the Emperor of Verze,
will then be installed as the...
Do not say that!
Yes, your highness.
Some assistance, m'lady?
Never have I been pleased with the blood
that continues to flow through my veins.
I find it to be repugnant.
Is the only reason I am being kept alive
because of the value of my blood?
A tool used just to activate the old Noah?
Apologies, your highness.
There is no apology necessary.
It was you who extended the hand of friendship.
I am very grateful for that, Lord Count.
Even if my blood receives only curses,
you have nothing but my thanks.
Slain.
Yes, may I be of service?
You may.
Would you be able to teach me more about the earth?
With great pleasure.
Looks like we're together again, huh?
Yeah.
I hope that we're all gonna make it back alive again.
Mm-hmm.
We are not gonna be dying.
We'll beat the Martians.
We'll beat them and see to what peace comes back.
For everyone.
We won't have the spare time to die.
I guess not.
Hostile Martian cataphract.
Incoming.
Radar return confirmed.
20 clicks to the south.
Closing speed 50 kph.
All hands to battle stations.
The ship is leaving the dock.
But the anti-gravity device is being serviced.
Very sorry I'm late.
Wait, what are those garments you're wearing?
Where's the uniform you were issued?
Well, that uniform's really not cute.
It's not cute.
I'll allow it.
It's not going to hinder her ability to handle the helm.
Captain, really?
Mizusaki.
You think that's why you have such trouble getting a date?
Deucalion, activate.
Cataphract squadron, launch all ready units.
What do we know about him?
Identified as Baron Yacom's cataphract frozen elysium.
The unique capability of the Alt Noah drive on this
is identified as entropy dilution.
What is that?
It's able to stop the molecular motion of all matter
within a radius of one kilometer.
It saps all heat so everything freezes.
Even the air.
All right, Terran fools.
Show me how you dare defy the power of Alt Noah.
At its current rate of speed,
it'll reach where the Deucalion's docked in 15 minutes.
We've got to find some way to slow it down.
Slow it down?
You're joking, right?
We're going to destroy that thing.
This is Harbinger platoon.
Target is spotted.
Rig for cold weather mode.
Turbine outputs are set to max.
De-icers on high.
Commencing attack.
What's this?
Wait, why aren't the De-icers working?
That can't be.
You are helpless.
It is not for nothing that the name is Frozen Elysium.
Voltage is falling.
The electrical reaction in my batteries is stopped.
My hand.
No.
My gun.
Carpenter leader!
Bastard!
It doesn't look like our rounds are even connecting!
It's got a shield.
It's not on the profile.
We're out of options!
This is bad.
We need to think of a way to slow it down.
I thought you said we were going to destroy the damn thing!
Call it a downward revision.
Measuring vector change.
You can fall back.
That goes for you both.
Oh, now I get it.
The warheads entered a superconductive state
and were repelled by the Meisner effect.
Let's see how airburst mode works.
All duds?
Oh, right, the warhead batteries froze.
And then all the processors locked up.
Where does the sapped heat go?
It must be shunting the energy from molecular movement
to another location.
Flight distance for the warhead's electronic timer fuse.
Fifty meters should do it.
Radius of the entropy field, one kilometer.
Exactly.
So then 20 rounds should do the job.
Inaho!
I'm going to take care of this.
But he'll breathe you!
I just need to reach him before then.
Wait!
Very amusing.
Come then.
Midair burst mode set for the grenade launcher.
Safe distance setting canceled.
Flight distance 50 meters.
Fire.
Oh.
Isn't there a啦?
Hmph.
Look!
Move on!
WE'VE THE END
T
Well done.
Inahou!
I took more damage than I expected.
I wonder what Kham will say.
Inahou!
Are you alright, Inahou?
Ensign Inahou Kaisuka. Reporting as ordered.
Per UFV General Headquarters, I am assigned to your ship.
Come on, what's with that stuff?
You never change, but I like that.
Right back at you. And Inko, you look very good.
You have changed. A lot.
Look at you making polite social chit-chat and small talk.
You know, that's not really a compliment.
Inko...
Inko.
Welcome back.
Welcome back, Inahou.
Good to be back.
Go ahead. Slain.
Slain.
I just killed the Terran who has been such a problem for us.
I have finally made up my mind.
Please forgive me for the wrongs I have done you in the past, and will do in the future.
My lord, Count Sazbaum.
It seems that Terran troops have successfully breached the castle.
Let us escape in the Tharsis.
We'll take the princess with us.
I am the only one who can save you now, my lord.
Will you die without meeting your goal?
Or will you live along with Princess Asalem?
Your decision.
Your highness, are you—
What's this?
No!
Inahou!
Yuki!
Inahou's been—
He's—
Dr. Yagarai, you have to do something!
Is that Inahou?
Gunshot wound to the head.
Bullet went through the temporal region via the left eye socket.
He's unconscious.
Administer three cc's of adrenaline.
This is bad.
You're gonna save him, right?
You're gonna save Inahou's life, aren't you, doctor?
He needs immediate emergency surgical treatment and a transfusion.
But there's no—
We have all the facilities and tools we need in the underground shelter.
Captain Magbarej, hurry!
Order the Deucalion to lift off!
The old Noah Drive.
It's—
It's not working now.
Warrant Officer Kaiska.
Princess Asalem.
Where is she?
Ah heres—
Ah haa!
Ah ha!
Ah ha ha!
Ah ha ha !
Wait!
Ah ha ha!
that blood is that blood nose no not his
it's blood spatter but whose
that's
that is the light of alt noah
he can activate it
now
Deucalion lift off engage dead slow to start
all ahead dead slow to start
out of the atmosphere making way on
inertia course set for trident base
electromagnetic grid monitor all
wavelengths
the Terrans who squandered the goodwill
of the verse Empire are biding their
time before attempting to steal our
lands from us
the verse Empire must exterminate them
out of mercy we have to fight her
it's our only choice in a home
the abundant air and water diffract the
light to make the sky and sea appear to
that's wrong
the sky appears blue from Rayleigh scattering
water please Adele Ritzo
yes milady right away
do you think that was satisfactory
count Sosbone
I do you were the very image of
princesses Salem no one would ever
suspect your true identity
this is the problem with you men
there was no mention by anyone of any
true identities
that was masterfully done princess
Lemrina your words were majestic
they must have greatly moved the
orbital knights
why thank you
sir slain Troyard
I am more grateful for such insight as
that than compliments on my performance
I am very humbled and delighted
it's because I watched my elder sister
very closely although unfortunately I
never got to meet her while she was
still alive
oh do please forgive me you and my
sister were close were you not
I thank you for your concern
please try not to take offense my lord
slain princess Lemrina meant no harm
I know I understand that her family
relationship is a burden to her
if there is nothing else my lord I will
take my leave
thank you once again mr. harplight
I have returned princess of Salem
I see you are doing well
you are doing well
you are difficult to find her
come on tell me when we are here
This endless party war
Why I cry in the sky
But you got to know
Little boy
Just stop what you're doing for me
It's not very good for you
We should know where we are
When nobody knows
Fly high
How will God last in me
Rule let's fall like rain
Our chance is like a shooting star
You can feel something in your heart
Everything is written around the world
Break your door together
The other side
Let's see anything you can leave
The only one
And it's always been so good
And it's all good for me
And everyone's around
They want to take my hand